mattressclarity.com 2019-05-16

# Privacy Policy - Mattress Clarity

## Introduction

This privacy policy (“Policy”) and this site’s Terms of Service (together the “Terms”) govern all use of [https://www.mattressclarity.com](https://www.mattressclarity.com/) and that site’s services (together the “Site” or “Services”). The owners and contributors to the Site will be referred to as “we,” “us,” or “our” in this Policy. By using the Site or its Services, and/or by clicking anywhere on this Site to agree to the Terms and this Policy, you are deemed to be a “user” for purposes of this Policy. You and every other user (“you” or “User” as applicable) are subject to this Policy. You and each user also agree to the Terms by using the Services. In these Terms, the word “Site” includes the site referenced above, its owner(s), contributors, suppliers, licensors, and other related parties.

We provide this privacy statement explaining our online information practices, so that you can decide whether and how to interact with the Site and the Services.

We may release your information when we deem it appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others’ rights, property, or safety.

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

Please also review our Terms of Use section that governs the use and the users of the Site.

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. If we have your email address, we may also send an email notifying you of any changes.

#####  **Contact Details:**

Full Name Of Legal Entity: JAKK MEDIA LLC

Email Address: m a t t r e s s c l a r i t y @ g m a i l . c o m

Postal Address: 201 W 5th St. #1100, Austin, TX, 78701

## Contact Data and Other Identifiable Information

This site collects certain user information, which may include a username and password, contact information, or any other data that you type in to the site. It may also identify your IP address to help identify you on future visits to the site. At our discretion, the Site may use this data to:

  * Personalize the user experience and/or customer service
  * Improve the site
  * To process transactions
  * Administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature or function
  * Send email to users
  * Inquiries (If you send us a comment or question or make an inquiry to customer support, we will retain the information that you provide to us for the purpose of responding to you, as well as for improving the Services and our customers’ use of our services.)
  * Web logs (We maintain web logs that automatically record basic information about everyone who visits the Services. We use web log information to help us design our website, to identify popular features, to improve our services, and for other managerial and analytic purposes. We may also use web logs to help identify any person who may be misusing the Services. These logs contain: The Internet domain from which you access the Services, your IP address, the type of browser and operating system that you use, the date and time you visited the Services, the pages that you visited on the Services, the address of the website you linked from to get to the Services)

## Sharing User Data

The site may share user data with third parties that  
help the site owner operate and manage the site,  
are the site owner’s advertisers and marketing partners,  
buy or rent data for purposes not limited to operating this site.

The site will only share such user data with these third parties in the aggregate, using collected data reporting on user activity and data that the site collects, but not identifying individual users. Information limited to or identifying individual site users will not be shared.

## Mobile Device Privacy

The following applies to our site, when viewed on a mobile device:  
When accessed with a mobile deivce, our site may collect information automatically, such as the type of mobile device you have, device identifiers, and information about your use of the site. Regardless of the device you use to access the site, it will also collect information you provide, as well as information about your interaction with the site and its content.

If location services are activated on your mobile device, our site may collect information about the location of your device. Your mobile network service providers may collect device-specific information, such as a device identifier, when you use our website or one of our mobile applications. This information collected by your mobile network service will not be associated with your user account with us, or with your personally identifiable information.

## Protection of user information

We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you share with the site.

### Advertising Network

We use one or more third party vendors to serve ads on the Site. To serve ads and determine how our users use the Site, these services use cookies, or small pieces of code to serve ads to Site users based on users’ visits to the Site and others. Users may adjust their browser settings to disallow the use of cookies. With cookies turned off, certain features of the Site may work less efficiently or not at all.

We use Google as an advertising services provider for the Site. Users may opt out of Google’s use of the DART use-tracking cookie by visiting the Google advertising Policies & Principles page. If you opt out of ad tailoring, you will still see ads, but they will not be based on your browsing history, and they may appear in other languages.

### Cookies

This site uses cookies. Cookies are small pieces of code that the Site or a service provider will put on your computer if your Web browser allows it. The Site uses cookies to recognize and keep certain information. On the Site, that information may be used to recognize your computer and browser from current or past visits to the Site or related sites. We may use this cookie-captured information to improve our service to you, to aggregate information about visitors to the Site and their behavior, to remember and process items in your shopping cart, to understand and save user preferences, or to keep track of advertising. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors.  
In most Internet browsers, you can change your settings so that you will be warned each time a cookie is being sent, or so that cookies will be turned off. With cookies blocked, some functions of the Site may not operate properly.

See Our [Full Cookie Policy](https://www.mattressclarity.com/cookies-policy/)

## Usernames, Passwords, and Profiles

If prompted, Users must provide a valid email address to the Site, at which the User can receive messages. User must also update the Site if that email address changes. The Site reserves the right to terminate any User account if a valid email is requested but is not provided by the User.

If the Site prompts or allows a User to create a username or profile, Users agree not to pick a username or provide any profile information that would impersonate someone or that is likely to cause confusion with any other person or entity. The Site reserves the right to cancel a User account or change a username or profile data at any time. Similarly, if the Site prompts or allows a User to create an avatar or upload a picture, User agrees not to use any image that impersonates some other person or entity, or that is otherwise likely to cause confusion.

You are responsible for protecting your username and password for the Site, and you agree not to disclose it to any third party. We recommend that you use a password that is more than eight characters long. You are responsible for all activity on your account, whether or not you authorized it. You agree to inform us of unauthorized use of your account, by email to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) You acknowledge that if you wish to protect your interactions the Site, it is your responsibility to use a secure encrypted connection, virtual private network, or other appropriate measures.

## Disputes

We are based in Austin, TX and you are contracting to use our Site. This Policy and all matters arising from your use of the Site are governed by and will be construed according to the laws of Austin, TX, without regard to any choice of laws rules of any jurisdiction. The federal courts and state courts that have geographical jurisdiction over disputes arising at our office location in Austin, TX will be the only permissible venues for any and all disputes arising out of or in connection with this Policy or the Site and Service.

## Marketing Communications

Our lawful ground of processing your personal data to send you marketing communications is either your consent or our legitimate interests (namely to grow our business).

Before we share your personal data with any third party for their own marketing purposes we will get your express consent.

You can ask us or third parties to stop sending you marketing messages at any time by clicking the unsubscribe button at the bottom of our emails or by sending us an email at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

If you opt out of receiving marketing communications this opt-out does not apply to personal data provided as a result of other transactions, such as purchases, warranty registrations etc.

 **Browser notifications**

Browser notifications are managed by a third party software. If you have opted in for browser notifications (pop-up on your device when an article is published), you may opt out of these by following the general instructions below. Note these instructions may vary between browser versions and devices:

 _ **Desktop**_

 **In Chrome** , navigate to Settings, then navigate to Advanced. Select Content Settings under Privacy and Security. Select Notifications, where you can manage specific site notifications under “Block” and “Allow”. If you would like to turn off notifications for the Site, select the Site’s listing, then check “Block.”

 **In Firefox,  **navigate to the menu and select Options. Navigate to Privacy & Security. Navigate to Permissions and then click Notifications Settings, where you can turn off notifications for individual sites.

 **In Safari** , navigate to Preferences, then Websites and then Notifications, where you can pick which sites are able to send you notifications.

 **On Android Mobile Devices,  **open the Chrome browser and navigate to Menu, then navigate to Settings. Navigate to Site Settings and then Notifications, where you can determine which sites you’d like to allow notifications for. On the following screen, select clear & reset, then click your preferred options.

## How We Use Your Information

Here is how we may use your information and data:

 **Communicating with You.**  We may use information that we collect from you for the purpose of communicating with you and responding to your inquiries. Those communications could, for example, take the form of service updates, promotions for products or services that we or one of our marketing partners provide, or e-newsletters.

 **Service Providers:**  We at times contract with third party service providers to perform functions for us. These service providers may be given access to the information we collect for the purpose of performing those functions, but they will be contractually bound to maintain the confidentiality of the information and not to use it for any other purpose.

 **Social Media.**  The Sites may include social media features, such as Facebook “Like” button and a “Share” button. These features may collect your IP address and which page you are visiting on the Site; and they may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company that provides the feature.

 **Business Transfers:**  If we were to transfer all or substantially all of our assets to another company, one of the assets we would likely include in the transfer is our database of Personal Information.

 **Disclosures for Legal Reasons:**  We will disclose Personal Information when we are required to do so by law, regulation or securities exchange requirement, for example, in response to a court order or subpoena. We also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency’s request or when we believe such disclosure is appropriate to protect our legal rights or to safeguard anyone’s property or safety.

## How We Share Information And Why

We may have to share your personal data with the parties set out below:

* Other companies in our group who provide services to us.

* Other companies in our group who provide services to us.

* Professional advisers including lawyers, bankers, auditors and insurers

* Government bodies that require us to report processing activities

* With third party advertising platforms so that we can create marketing campaign advertising (e.g. using your email address to create a Facebook targeting audience).

* When you participate in interactive area of our website, service, and products, and your information may be displayed to other users: such information may include, your name, photo, the comment, and other information you chose to provide at the time of submission. In the case of Surveys, we will never share personally identifiable information without express consent.

* In response to a request for information if we believe disclosure is in accordance with, or required by, any applicable law, regulation or legal process;

* If we believe your actions are inconsistent with our user agreements or policies, or to protect the rights, property and safety of Company or others;

* Third parties to whom we sell, transfer, or merge parts of our business or our assets.

* With your consent or at your direction.

We require all third parties to whom we transfer your data to respect the security of your personal data and to treat it in accordance with the law. We only allow such third parties to process your personal data for specified purposes and in accordance with our instructions.

## International Transfers

We are subject to the provisions of the General Data Protection Regulations that protect your personal data. Where we transfer your data to third parties outside of the EEA, we will ensure that certain safeguards are in place to ensure a similar degree of security for your personal data. As such:

* We may transfer your personal data to countries that the European Commission have approved as providing an adequate level of protection for personal data by; or

* If we use US-based providers that are part of EU-US Privacy Shield, we may transfer data to them, as they have equivalent safeguards in place; or

* Where we use certain service providers who are established outside of the EEA, we may use specific contracts or codes of conduct or certification mechanisms approved by the European Commission which give personal data the same protection it has in Europe.

If none of the above safeguards is available, we may request your explicit consent to the specific transfer. You will have the right to withdraw this consent at any time.

## Terms Contact

If you have any questions about these Terms, please address them to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) or to the below address:

Attention: Joe Auer, Mattress Clarity  
201 W 5th Street #1100 STE 49  
Austin, TX, 78701

## Last Updated

These terms were last updated on  _March 22nd, 2019_
